<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">H2O Studioz</string>

    <string name="Address">H2O Dance and Fitness Studioz \n CJR Arcade, Second Floor \n Next to Bangalore Central Mall \n
        Outer Ring Rd, Bellandur \n Bengaluru, Karnataka - 560103</string>

    <string name="Story_of_h2o">H2O STUDIOZ was founded in 2014 by Mr. Karthik. We concentrate on giving a Quality
        teaching in all the services we provide and make sure there is a good learning and constant growth in the individual.\n\n
        We always aim higher in everything and we foresee ourself to be the best dance and fitness institute in the coming future and
        spreading our wings across various parts of the city and county.\n\n
        Dream is to follow passion towards dance and help others to follow theirs!
        We look forward to welcome you to be a part of our fun filled family.
    </string>

    <string name="kavya">A Post graduate in Computer Science and working as a Software Engineer in a reputed company, still she continues her passion towards singing at H2O Studioz. Music was there always in her right from her childhood days. She is Trained in Carnatic music and she has represented herself in many of the tv shows and also in a band where she used to perform as a lead female singer. She is the main instructor who handles the singing classes at the Studio. </string>

    <string name="karthik">Founder / Artistic Director / Principal Choreographer of H2O Studioz. His Love towards Dance and to spread happiness through it was the main intension to start this dance and fitness studio. Being a post graduate in management studies with ample of corporate job experience his love towards Dance and the dream of starting the Dance institute never stopped and he aimed in building a studio with friendly atmosphere and involve everyone to be as a part of one big family\n\n
    He is a Trained Dancer in various Dance styles for over 7 years now. He is also a Certified Zumba B1, Aqua Zumba, Strong by Zumba, Masala Bhangra fitness Instructor. Participated in various National and international level competitions and won many prizes.</string>

    <string name="ramesh">Dance Instructor in Freestyle and Bollywood. Expertise in handling kids batch at H2O. He is a professional dance teacher in Christ School, Bangalore.</string>

    <string name="nidhi_abhishek">Nidhi Agarwal and Abhishek Singh
Nidhi and Abhishek, having danced together only for over a year now, have represented India and have placed in top positions at many Championships together in Salsa and Bachata. Their recent victories were at India International Dance Congress 2015, Singapore International Latin Festival 2016 and The World Salsa Summit 2016</string>

    <string name="Deeptha">Hi, I\'m Deeptha. I am currently working as a Software Engineer in Accenture. I have had my utmost fondness for Dance since my childhood. One thing I\’m sure about in my life is that the more I dance, the more I feel happy and alive. It gives me great pride and ecstasy to say that I am a clan member of H2O since June\’17. It has been till now and sure going to be, an exciting journey in H2O for me with truly inspiring, devoted and high-spirited dancers around. I am trained in classical dance (Bharatanatyam). Right now I\’m so excited that I\’m exploring different other dance forms. Million thanks and Cheers to H2O for keeping passion and dreams of many alive!! </string>

    <string name="Kailas">Hello, myself Kailas. I\'m a freestyler. For me dance is like an emotion. And I\'ll be on my toes to dance. H2O means water, and water dissolves many of the things, similar is the atmosphere created here in H2O, you\'ll get dissolved here and form bonds with everyone. My skills have improved significantly since I joined here and I ended up getting into The H2O Clan.</string>

    <string name="Brindha_Sundar">I am Brindha, Salesforce developer at Unisys. I discovered my love for dance as a kid but I was unable to pursue it. Once settled at work, I, along with my friends, did a vigorous search for classes and that was when H2O popped up. One trial class was all that was needed to spark the excitement. With lot of learning ever since, one year later, I landed in the H2O Clan after clearing an audition. I could see my confidence build up in every performance since then. Why H2O? H2O helped in finding the dancer in me and has never ceased its encouragement and support. Dance styles: Hiphop, Bollywood, Freestyle, Tamil folk</string>

    <string name="Ajay">I am an application developer in TCS. I was a shy person who never danced. My friends convinced me to join dance classes with them. My moves were sloppy in the beginning , but persistence and Karthik\'s classes made me perform a solo for his auditions. I cleared it making a place for myself in H2O\'s clan. It was a great step for me to come out of my comfort zone. I find dance as a way of expressing myself and also a way of losing the extra calories that I gain occasionally.</string>

    <string name="Varun">I am Varun. I am an application developer in IBM. I have been wanting to learn dance since when I was a kid. It was an unfulfilled dream which turned dormant. After I started working I started to search for dance classes along with some of my friends. We stumbled upon H2O and there has been no turning back. I never expected that I would find the sense of belonging that I feel in H2O. I ended up trying for the auditions to join H2O\'s clan and got selected. My love for dance has increased since I started and would never give it up for any reason.</string>

    <string name="Yogesh">I really enjoying and learning while dancing with very passionate and creative team of dancer in H2O clan. Karthik strives to bring the motivation and leadership to make the best dance form out of us . Also his zumba talent helping us big time to stay fit and flexible which help to make our dance perfectly and on professional level.</string>

    <string name="Ramita_Ahmed">Hi, I am Ramita. I am working as an HR professional with Synechron Technologies.The only thing I know about my life is Dance- I live to Dance! My dance form is Kathak. With H20, I got in touch with many dance forms.. and the first day I joined H20, I just knew I can continue my talent here and learn more. I am so glad I got a chance to be a part of H20 clan. We are like a  part of a small family with extremely talented dancers. I am sure this clan will go places. We Rock!!</string>

    <string name="Akshatha_mahadev">I am a Software Engineer working in Infosys. Dance has always been my passion. And now dance has kind of become a part of my routine. And fortunately, I came across H2O 2 years back for both Zumba and Dance and now I am a proud member of the H2O Clan. I\'ve also got to learn different forms of dance here like Contemporary, Hip-Hop and Bollywood.</string>

    <string name="Neha_Gupta">We Dance to heal. \n We dance to feel. \n We dance to express. \n I dance because dancing is life. \n
        I dance because there is nothing else that engages me the same way physically, emotionally and socially all at once. And it all happens at H2O Studioz.
        I\’m a Software Engineer by profession and a dancer by passion. I originally started to dance with H2O by learning Contemporary dance form and Zumba for fitness. Being my first dance class, I learnt all possible dance forms. Be it contemporary, Bollywood, salsa or hip-hop.
        Dance provides self-confidence. And it was witnessed when I started taking classes. From a non-dancer to a member of H2O Clan, it\’s been an exciting journey of 3 years. Happy to be a part of H2O Family</string>

    <string name="Shilpa">They say dance to the beats of the music.But here at H2O we say dance to the beats of your dreams.The energy and passion in the people of this institute makes you fall in love with dancing. Be it Bollywood, contemporary,hip hop or Zumba here we can learn all the dance forms at it best. I joined here in search for a place where I could enjoy my hobby but soon realized that my hobby has become my life.</string>

    <string name="Natesan_Sivagnanam">I take care of Product User Interface Development at SAP Labs India. I have been dancing for little over a year now, I prefer Bollywood, Contemporary and Freestyle. The environment at H2O is simply amazing and getting into Clan just slivers it into another stage altogether.</string>

    <string name="Vinoth_Kannan">One of the best things to happen to me in Bangalore is H2O studioz. It is not just dance that happens, it\'s a lot more. I call it H2O Family. The one thing that binds this Family is the art of expression. For the strength of family is dance and the strength of dance is the family.</string>

    <string name="Praveena">I am a freelance fashion designer and fashion entrepreneur, choreographer and performing artist. I began my training in dance during my early childhood like Bharatanatyam, mohiniyattam, folk , fusion etc. I am trained in Bharatanatyam. I believe dance is my life and it is divine gift to me. It is my honour that I am being associated with H2O. I am always excited to bring my passion for dance in the studio, to encourage creativity and highest potential team.</string>
    
    <string name="Banashree">I am working as an Application Support Analyst in Epicor, Bangalore. Dance makes me feel free, away from all my anxieties, connected to myself, happy! I always wanted to join a dance class and H2O fitted all my requirements. And meeting everyone here I realized we all are connected through a beautiful form of expression- Dance! I like to dance to the beats of Bollywood and Hip-Hop but I would also I like explore the beauty of contemporary.</string>

    <string name="Narmadha">I am Narmadha, a software engineer at Toshiba. My passion for dancing began at college and grew with lot of performances. After I passed out of college, I thought my passion would also pass out of me, yet somehow, it came back and knocked my door by means of friends and H2O. Out of the regular classes here, I got back my dancing spirit and began noticing a lot of improvement. Gradually my improvements got me into the H2O clan and I can proudly say that joining H2O was one of the best decisions I had ever made.</string>

    <string name="Bhanu">Updating Soon.....</string>

    <string name="Himadri">Hello dancers. I am himadri deva and I work as an instructional designer at Ernst n Young (EY). I have only one passion and is dance and only dance. I have been dancing on Bollywood numbers from the age of 3 and have won many awards in school and college. I was the cultural minister in my college. For me dance is the best way to shed anything, be it calories or stress. I wanted to join some dance studio and continue my passion. H2O gave me the platform. I feel so motivated and energetic when throughout the day when I dance in the morning. Being a part of this amazing dance team has made me even more positive and energetic ( getting more compliments from people around me). Thanks to Karthik and the wonderful clan for making me a part of them and shaping me.</string>

    <string name="Shruthi">I am Shruti and I am a Software Engineer and dance has been my passion always.I can\'t imagine my life without dance and that\'s when I tried to find a dance class  and I am glad that I found H2O Studioz with a instructor like Karthik.I had immense love for Contemporary dance form,wanted to learn and Karthik has been great part in being such a great instructor to have guided me so well.I would love and continue to be part of H2O family,especially be a part of H2O Clan which would help me mould to become a better dancer.Its great to be part of Clan which has amazing and dedicated dancers,looking forward for experiencing a better dancer in me.</string>

    <string name="bollywood">Take your waves, footwork, and grooves to a whole new level by focusing on your musicality and timing. You can even combine them with other styles like jump style, tecktonic, hip hop, etc. In bollywood/FreeStyle/Hip-hop class, you will learn how to put all these moves together!!</string>

    <string name="contemporary">Feel your soul in this form of dance !!</string>

    <string name="salsa">Learn how to groove with Salsa !!</string>
    
    <string name="kids">Let your kids move their feet in H2O Studioz !!</string>

    <string name="zumba">Take your waves, footwork, and grooves to a whole new level by focusing on your musicality and timing. You can even combine them with other styles like jump style, tecktonic, hip hop, etc. In bollywood/FreeStyle/Hip-hop class, you will learn how to put all these moves together!!</string>

    <string name="yoga">Feel your soul in this form of dance !!</string>

    <string name="masala">Learn how to groove with Salsa !!</string>

    <string name="aqua">Let your kids move their feet in H2O Studioz !!</string>

    <string name="carnatic">Take your waves, footwork, and grooves to a whole new level by focusing on your musicality and timing. You can even combine them with other styles like jump style, tecktonic, hip hop, etc. In bollywood/FreeStyle/Hip-hop class, you will learn how to put all these moves together!!</string>

    <string name="corporate">Feel your soul in this form of dance !!</string>

    <string name="wedding">Learn how to groove with Salsa !!</string>

    <string name="workshop">Let your kids move their feet in H2O Studioz !!</string>

    <string name="flash">Let your kids move their feet in H2O Studioz !!</string>

    <string name="bollywood1">Bollywood/FreeStyle/Hip-hop</string>
    <string name="contemporary1">Contemporary</string>
    <string name="salsa1">Salsa</string>
    <string name="kids1">Kids FreeStyle</string>
    <string name="zumba1">Zumba</string>
    <string name="yoga1">Yoga</string>
    <string name="masala1">Masala Bhangra</string>
    <string name="aqua1">Aqua Zumba</string>
    <string name="carnatic1">Carnatic Music</string>
    <string name="corporate1">Corporate Events</string>
    <string name="wedding1">Wedding Choreos</string>
    <string name="workshop1">Zumba Workshops</string>
    <string name="flash1">Dance Performances/Flashmobs</string>

    
</resources>